Good morning.
Today, Sunday, April 16, is the last day of the Spring Tour Shinagawa Terrapole.
I'm in charge today,
The current time is 11:45. I have forgotten about the making of the tour until now,
I'd like to start turning it around a little bit from here.
I have just finished filming for Fanikon,
Rehearsals will start in a little while.
I will do my best!
Hello! This is Three's.
This is Shinagawa's today.
This is Blue Luli.
It's blue Luli.
I'm Browser Lynn.
And?
What?
Brothers!
We have about 20 minutes until rehearsal,
I don't know, I'm a little nervous because we're getting ready, or rather, we're done.
On the contrary, I'm nervous.
What am I going to do, what am I going to do?
I'll do my best!
Yes, please.
I want to keep hurting my little feelings.
I want to dream for a while longer.
The sunset we saw that day
And as time went by, I saw the children of the past
And you'll know it's love
Don't be a coward, stand strong
And see the freedom and the heart
I loved you just to be around you
You've fallen in love more times than you can count
The sky of love, you're gone
After the blue tears of spring
Sosia's treason Someone's grasping
Sosia's treason, someone's grasping
♪ Lost in the shadows, indeed
My hands are shaking I love you
I've got a bag full of shoes that I can't put on.
Whichever one it is, every day is a tension
The woman of the sliding world
First time in principle
Expectation talk judges the other side
Already I've lost my mind about tomorrow.
I don't continue to imagine.
It's a balancing act.
A race to the finish line, a race to the finish line.
The day we met, people were a little different
I don't want to forget that we still feel the same way.
I'm sure you're looking at the petals of my dream
To the place that still has no name.
Yes, rehearsal is over.
It's over.
Oh, that was a little bit loud.
How was it?
What did you think of the rehearsal?
Well, the stage was huge.
The stage was huge.
It was big,
Also, I see this is coming up too.
We played a new song,
I don't know what was the strongest.
It was good.
Because the new songs are really good.
I was looking forward to it, and I thought it would be a lot of fun when the audience came.
Any feedback?
Yes, so the show is on!
Congratulations!
I'm looking forward to it.
It's the last day of my 5 stops already, so I'm looking forward to it!
All I've said is I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good luck and let's end with a very successful Love Parade.
Well, I'm off!
Bye bye!
I can do it, I can do it! Good luck everyone!
Bye bye!Bye-bye.
I've been hiding even the no-no's.
On that side of my route
A new star is born now
A girl knows it's over the rail
This year, again, people in the city are turning inside out
I'll like you more than I know
Turn around before your voice reaches someone else
Just like last year... the moon is smiling a little today.
Don't listen to me, before the sound of that call echoes down the hall.
I know that I can take the first step toward you.
Rail Over
Beloved.
[applause]
Thank you for your hard work today.
Well, I mean, there are only four of us here, but...
Did you have a good time? Spring tour
It was fun.
It was good.
When did you start thinking about it?
It was really fun every time.
It was fun.
That was a stoma, wasn't it?
I feel like we made a lot of memories.
Yes, we did.
How's it going? When it's over...
I feel a sense of accomplishment.
I mean, it's pretty satisfying.
We did it ourselves.
It feels like we did it ourselves.
There was a sense of dokugo.
It made me want to take the next step.
The next story has already begun.
It's already started.
So I'm already acing it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
For coming.
Bye.
Yes, so thank you very much for listening to Haltz.
Well, today is the last day of the show.
We're going to start releasing new songs next week.
The first single for the major label has also been distributed.
I hope you will support us even more from now on!
And now, I've sent you the making of each comment so far.
Thank you very much for your patience.
Thank you very much.
I didn't do much editing.
No, no, no, no, no.
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
You know what?
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much.
See you all on site.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.